https://sewwhatinc.com/privacy/

Privacy | Sew What? Inc.
Skip to content
FacebookFlickrYouTubeInstagramPinterestLinkedInBlogger
Call today (310) 639-6000 | Contact Us
Sew What? It's not a question.
It's the answer.
Custom ProductsStage DrapesCustom SewingBackdropsDigital PrintingLED StardropsPipe & DrapeTension Fabric ShapesCurtain TrackTheater SuppliesPoliciesRental InventorySpecialty Drapery CollectionsSilver SatinIndustrial TexturesRockin’ RedTimeless & TraditionalOh’ So Swanky!Delightably WhiteStardropsBlack Masking Drapes & BordersPipe & DrapeKabuki Solenoid SystemsLift SystemsTraveler TrackPop-Up! Portable Dressing RoomsRental Terms & FAQ’sStorage ServicesResourceseSwatchesVelours & VelvetsDuvetyne & CommandoScenic FabricScrim & LenoSheers, Satins, SilksStretch FabricsMasking, Blackout LiningEvents & Display FabricsOutdoor FabricsPrintable FabricsAlphabetical IndexPortfoliosDrape DescriptionsGrand DrapeStage BackdropTravelerTableauContourAustrian/BrailleTeaser/TormentorsLegs/BorderScrimCycloramaFlame RetardancySew What? BlogWhite PapersAbout UsPress RoomTestimonialsEmploymentSew What? BlogContact UsMASKS
Search for:
Custom ProductsStage DrapesCustom SewingBackdropsDigital PrintingLED StardropsPipe & DrapeTension Fabric ShapesCurtain TrackTheater SuppliesPoliciesRental InventorySpecialty Drapery CollectionsSilver SatinIndustrial TexturesRockin’ RedTimeless & TraditionalOh’ So Swanky!Delightably WhiteStardropsBlack Masking Drapes & BordersPipe & DrapeKabuki Solenoid SystemsLift SystemsTraveler TrackPop-Up! Portable Dressing RoomsRental Terms & FAQ’sStorage ServicesResourceseSwatchesVelours & VelvetsDuvetyne & CommandoScenic FabricScrim & LenoSheers, Satins, SilksStretch FabricsMasking, Blackout LiningEvents & Display FabricsOutdoor FabricsPrintable FabricsAlphabetical IndexPortfoliosDrape DescriptionsGrand DrapeStage BackdropTravelerTableauContourAustrian/BrailleTeaser/TormentorsLegs/BorderScrimCycloramaFlame RetardancySew What? BlogWhite PapersAbout UsPress RoomTestimonialsEmploymentSew What? BlogContact UsMASKS
Search for:
Custom ProductsStage DrapesCustom SewingBackdropsDigital PrintingLED StardropsPipe & DrapeTension Fabric ShapesCurtain TrackTheater SuppliesPoliciesRental InventorySpecialty Drapery CollectionsSilver SatinIndustrial TexturesRockin’ RedTimeless & TraditionalOh’ So Swanky!Delightably WhiteStardropsBlack Masking Drapes & BordersPipe & DrapeKabuki Solenoid SystemsLift SystemsTraveler TrackPop-Up! Portable Dressing RoomsRental Terms & FAQ’sStorage ServicesResourceseSwatchesVelours & VelvetsDuvetyne & CommandoScenic FabricScrim & LenoSheers, Satins, SilksStretch FabricsMasking, Blackout LiningEvents & Display FabricsOutdoor FabricsPrintable FabricsAlphabetical IndexPortfoliosDrape DescriptionsGrand DrapeStage BackdropTravelerTableauContourAustrian/BrailleTeaser/TormentorsLegs/BorderScrimCycloramaFlame RetardancySew What? BlogWhite PapersAbout UsPress RoomTestimonialsEmploymentSew What? BlogContact UsMASKS
Home/Privacy
Privacy
Privacy Policy
Sew What? recognizes and respects its customers’ privacy. This privacy policy demonstrates our commitment to your privacy rights. We want you to fully understand the terms and conditions surrounding the gathering of information about our customers.
Sew What? may use any information voluntarily given by our users to enhance our website. We may create internal reports on user demographics and traffic patterns for our own use. This information will not be disclosed to any third parties. We may collect personally identifiable information (for example, your name, email address, mailing address, telephone number, or mobile phone number) from you when you submit a form from our web site or subscribe to our blog feed. We need this information in order to respond to your needs.
About Cookies.
Non-personal information may also be collected from you by means of Cookies. Cookies are small bits of information that this site places on your computer. We use cookies to identify your IP address browser type, domain name, and specific web pages through which you click. This data is collected automatically and utilized to help us look for trends to improve our site and your interactive experience. The cookies allow us to recognize you when you return to the site and to provide you with a customized experience that we feel will be of value to you. The cookies that are configured by this site do not contain any sensitive personally identifying information. Additional information regarding browser cookies and how to disable them is described below.
What Information Do We Share and with Whom?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. We may release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property, or safety.
Can I Disable Cookies?
Most web browsers allow you to exercise control over cookie files on your computer by erasing them, blocking them, or notifying you when such a file is stored. Please take a look at your particular browser for instructions on this function. If you do elect to disable cookies, please note that you may not be able to take full advantage of a personalized shopping experience on this Site.
What About Links To Other Sites
This site may contain links to other sites. Sew What? Inc. is not responsible for the privacy practices of other non-affiliated sites. You should read the privacy statements of each and every site that collects personally identifiable information.
Is My Information Secure?
We maintain reasonable and appropriate physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect your information. We make no warranties, express, implied or otherwise as to the ultimate effectiveness of these reasonable and appropriate safeguards.
Can I “Opt-Out” of Receiving Promotional E-mails
If you would no longer like to receive e-mails, sales notifications or other promotional messages from this site, you can unsubscribe by following the unsubscribe link located at the bottom of each promotional e-mail. Your e-mail address will be removed from this Site’s email marketing list within 10 days.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
We may modify this Privacy Policy to reflect industry initiatives or changes in the law, changes in our practices, or changes in our site’s features or technology. Your continued use of this site after we post a revised Privacy Policy signifies your acceptance of the revised Privacy Policy. It is therefore important that you review this Privacy Policy regularly to ensure you are updated as to any changes.
Copyright 1999 - 2020 Sew What? Inc. - All rights reserved.
Sew What? Inc., 1978 Gladwick Street, Rancho Dominguez, CA 90220
Phone: (310) 639-6000 Fax: (310) 639-6036
Site Map | Privacy
FacebookFlickrYouTubeInstagramPinterestLinkedInBlogger
Go to Top
